

Tehran, IRAN

🛮 (+98) 935-4536361 | 🗷 hamed.zaghaghi@gmail.com | 🖸 github.com/zaghaghi | 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/zaghaghi/

"Help Machine Learning Researchers To Build Production Ready Softwares and Services."

Summary

Experienced C/C++ and Python developer and team leader with a demonstrated history of working in the artificial intelligence industry. Skilled in Machine Learning, Computer Science and Linux Programming.

Areas Of Expertise

Team Management Agile Methodolgy, Scrum Framework

Back End Development C/C++, Python, POCO, Boost Front End Development Qt, JUCE, React Native Machine Learning Tensorflow, Kaldi

DevOps Docker, Docker Compose, Portainer, Kubernetes

Language Persian (Native), English (Professional working proficiency), French (Elementry)

Work Experience _

Amer Andish Hooshmand Tehran, Iran

CHIEF TECHNOLOGY OFFICER Jun. 2018 - Present

- · Expertly advise colleagues, mainly CEO, on new technologies and recent trends and researches in machine learning
- Help our machine learning researchers to build real-world services
- · Provide sound technical leadership in all aspects of company's business
- Discover new applications of machine learning in industry
- · Discover and implement new technologies that yield competitive advantage
- · Help colleagues use technology profitably
- · Deploy machine learning services in company's servers

Amer Andish Hooshmand Tehran, Iran

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER Jul. 2017 - Present

- · Serve as team leader and C++ developer for the "Botava", an enterprise chatbot platform with Farsi language support
- Implemented "Ordakak", a rule-based inverse text normalizer for Farsi language in Python
- · Implemented web services for "Farsava", an automatic Farsi speech recognition, in C++ using Kaldi library
- Implemented "Farsava" mobile application using React Native

Algodrill Tehran, Iran

C++ DEVELOPER | PART-TIME

2016 - 2017

- Developed a desktop client application in C++ using JUCE framework to view various charts and tables from "Algodrill" trading engine server
- · Developed a nosql database library for fast store and retrieve of time-series key-value data
- · Developed an order generator to test trading engine server

Douran Group Tehran, Iran

TEAM LEADER

2014 - 2017

- Developed Speech/Non-Speech Classifier in Python using Scikit-Learn library
- Developed a Farsi text classifier based on FastText library
- · Mostly Servered as team leader for machine learning section to help researchers develop production-ready services
- Served as team leader of an adult image detection service in Python using Caffe library
- · Acted as team leader for the creation of an in-house dashboard web application using HTML5, CSS and ReactJS

Douran Group Tehran, Iran C++ DEVELOPER 2011 - 2017

· Served as main developer of a high-bandwidth DDoS detection system in C and C++ using DPDK library

- Developed an IPS/IDS log analyzer in C++ using Poco and Fastbit libraries
- Served as C kernel developer of an IPS/IDS system
- · Developed adult image detection software from matlab codes written by machine learning researchers
- Developed a security visualization platform for plotting IPS/IDS logs and events in Java using Processing library

NOVEMBER 28, 2018 HAMED ZAGHAGHI **Payam-E-Noor University**

Mashhad, Iran

C++ & PYTHON LECTURER | PART-TIME 2009 - 2011

- · C++ Programming
- · Python Programming
- Computer Graphics

Belender Foundation Mashhad, Iran

C/C++ OPENSOURCE DEVELOPER | PART-TIME

2007 - 2011

- Developed real-time 2D filtering effects in Blender game engine, helping game makers using image effects in their games
- Developed sun/sky atmospheric scattering rendering in Blender internal render engine
- Developed a texture displacement system for realistic rendering of ocean waves, helping Promotion Studios to create "Light House" animated short movie

Education

Udacity udacity.com

SELF-DRIVING CAR NANODEGREE - 1ST TERM

2017

- Behavioral Cloning (source)
- Traffic Sign Classifier (source)
- Lane Line Detection (source)

University of Tehran Tehran, IRAN

MASTER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING - ALGORITHMS AND COMPUTATIONS

2008

· Thesis: Distributed Run-time Verification and its implementation on a Massively Multiplayer Online Game

Sadjad University of Technology

Mashhad, IRAN

BACHELORE'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

2005

• Thesis: Automated quality control for dashboard of peugeot 206 using image processing

Certificates

2015 **Professional Scrum Master**, Rayzan Samaneh Gostar

Tehran, IRAN

Honors & Awards

2005	5th place , First Nationwide Programming Contest	Mazandaran, IRAN
2003	9th place , ACM International Collegiate Programing Contest - Tehran Regional Contest.	Tehran, IRAN
2002	13th place , ACM International Collegiate Programing Contest - Tehran Regional Contest.	Tehran, IRAN